<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/</link><description>Recent content on Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 22:41:10 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.marshellyan.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pork Chop Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/pork-chop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 22:41:10 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/pork-chop/</guid><description>This recipe combines the crispy goodness of pan-fried pork chop with creamy spinach and blistered tomatoes for a flavorful and comforting meal. Let your taste buds travel through the southeastern United States with this delightful dish.
Chef Tip Tomatoes are a versatile ingredient that adds a lot of flavor to various cuisines. Although considered a fruit botanically, tomatoes are treated as a vegetable in cooking due to their savory taste. When eaten raw, tomatoes showcase their full flavor potential, offering a delightful combination of savory, sweet, and acidic notes.</description></item><item><title>Homemade Dog Food Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/dog-food-recipes/homemade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 19:44:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/dog-food-recipes/homemade/</guid><description>This recipe makes enough food for a medium-sized dog for one week. Adjust the portions according to your dog&amp;rsquo;s size and dietary needs.
Ingredients 1 pound ground turkey 1 cup brown rice 1 cup chopped carrots 1 cup chopped green beans 1 tablespoon fish oil 1/4 teaspoon salt Instructions In a large pot, cook the ground turkey over medium heat until browned. Add the brown rice, carrots, green beans, fish oil, and salt to the pot.</description></item><item><title>Meatball Spaghetti Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/meatball-spaghetti/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 21:23:52 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/meatball-spaghetti/</guid><description>Indulge in a classic comfort food with this delicious meatball spaghetti recipe. Tender homemade meatballs paired with flavorful tomato sauce and perfectly cooked spaghetti make for a satisfying and hearty meal.
Ingredients For the Meatballs: 1 pound ground beef 1/2 cup breadcrumbs 1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese 1/4 cup chopped fresh parsley 1/4 cup milk 1 egg 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 teaspoon dried oregano 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon black pepper For the Tomato Sauce: 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 small onion, finely chopped 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 can (28 ounces) crushed tomatoes 1 can (14 ounces) diced tomatoes 2 teaspoons dried basil 1 teaspoon dried oregano 1/2 teaspoon sugar Salt and pepper to taste For the Spaghetti: 8 ounces spaghetti noodles Salt for cooking pasta Grated Parmesan cheese for serving Chopped fresh basil for garnish (optional) Instructions Meatballs: In a large bowl, combine all the meatball ingredients (ground beef, breadcrumbs, Parmesan cheese, parsley, milk, egg, minced garlic, dried oregano, salt, and black pepper).</description></item><item><title>Pico De Gallo Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/sides/pico-de-gallo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 10:47:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/sides/pico-de-gallo/</guid><description>Enjoy the fresh and vibrant flavors of Pico de Gallo with this simple recipe. It&amp;rsquo;s a perfect accompaniment to tacos, burritos, or as a zesty topping for any Mexican dish.
Ingredients 4 medium ripe tomatoes, diced 1/2 cup finely chopped red onion 1/4 cup chopped fresh cilantro 2 tablespoons fresh lime juice 1 jalapeno pepper, finely chopped (seeds and membranes removed for a milder flavor) 1/2 teaspoon kosher salt Instructions In a mixing bowl, combine the diced tomatoes, red onion, chopped cilantro, lime juice, jalapeno pepper, and salt.</description></item><item><title>Guacamole Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/sides/guacamole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 10:42:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/sides/guacamole/</guid><description>Perfect as a dip or topping for your favorite Mexican dishes.
Ingredients 2 ripe Hass avocados 1/4 cup diced red onion 2 tablespoons chopped fresh cilantro 1 tablespoon fresh lime juice 1/2 teaspoon kosher salt 1/4 teaspoon ground cumin 1/4 teaspoon garlic powder 1/2 jalapeno pepper, seeded and finely chopped (optional) Instructions Cut the avocados in half lengthwise and remove the pits. Scoop out the avocado flesh into a mixing bowl.</description></item><item><title>Nutritional Value Template</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/cooking/nutritional-value-template/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 10:28:07 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/cooking/nutritional-value-template/</guid><description>Nutrient Amount Per Serving Calories xxx kcal Protein xx g Total Fat xx g Saturated Fat xx g Cholesterol xxx mg Total Carbohydrate xx g Dietary Fiber xx g Sugars xx g Sodium xxx mg Percent Daily Values are based on a 2,000-calorie diet. Your daily values may be higher or lower depending on your calorie needs.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Rice Bowl Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/chicken-rice-bowl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 10:21:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/chicken-rice-bowl/</guid><description>Ingredients For the Chicken:
1 pound boneless, skinless chicken thighs 1/4 cup olive oil 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 teaspoon cumin 1 teaspoon oregano 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/2 teaspoon salt For the Rice:
1 cup white rice 2 cups water 1/2 teaspoon salt 1 tablespoon lime juice 2 tablespoons chopped fresh cilantro For the Bowl:
1 cup cooked black beans 1 cup pico de gallo 1/2 cup shredded mozzarella cheese 1/2 cup guacamole 1/2 cup sour cream Instructions For the Chicken: Combine the chicken thighs, olive oil, minced garlic, cumin, oregano, black pepper, and salt in a bowl.</description></item><item><title>Recommended Cooking Oils</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/cooking/recommended-cooking-oils/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 09:57:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/cooking/recommended-cooking-oils/</guid><description>When it comes to selecting oils for cooking, we highly recommend using natural and wholesome options such as olive oil, avocado oil, and coconut oil. These oils offer numerous health benefits compared to chemically processed artificial oils like canola oil and vegetable oil. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at the advantages of using these healthier alternatives:
Olive Oil Olive oil is derived from pressing olives, making it a minimally processed oil.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Fettuccine Alfredo Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/chicken-fettuccine-alfredo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:05:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/food-recipes/meals/chicken-fettuccine-alfredo/</guid><description>This classic Italian dish is easy to make and perfect for a cozy dinner at home. This recipe serves four people.
Ingredients 1 pound fettuccine pasta 2 tablespoons butter 1 pound boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 cup heavy cream 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese Salt and pepper to taste Chopped parsley for garnish (optional) Instructions Cook the fettuccine pasta in a large pot of salted boiling water until al dente, according to package instructions.</description></item><item><title>Shadow's Food Recipe</title><link>https://docs.marshellyan.net/dog-food-recipes/shadow/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:43:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://docs.marshellyan.net/dog-food-recipes/shadow/</guid><description>This recipe makes enough food for a medium-sized dog for one week. Adjust the portions according to your dog&amp;rsquo;s size and dietary needs.
Ingredients 1 pound boneless chicken breasts 1 cup sweet potatoes 1/2 cup peas 2 cups white rice 8 oz cheddar cheese Instructions In a large pot, boil the chicken over medium heat until it reaches an internal temperature of 165°F. Use a shredder to shred the cooked chicken.</description></item></channel></rss>